<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: life | PND4]]></title>
  <link href="http://www.pnd4.net/blog/categories/life/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://www.pnd4.net/"/>
  <updated>2016-05-09T04:40:34-04:00</updated>
  <id>http://www.pnd4.net/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[pnd4]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[kevin@pnd4.net]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twenty-Thirteen]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.pnd4.net/blog/2013/01/11/twenty-thirteen/"/>
    <updated>2013-01-11T18:44:15-05:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.pnd4.net/blog/2013/01/11/twenty-thirteen</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><a href="/images/2013-01-11-twenty-thirteen/Screenshot-01112013-030931-PM-1024x288.png"><img src="/images/2013-01-11-twenty-thirteen/Screenshot-01112013-030931-PM-1024x288_th.png" alt="Jan 11 2013"></a>
Well, here it is.. my first post of 2013, located on my own domain from the awesome NameCheap.com, on a freshly set up Virtual Private Server by ChicagoVPS.net. So much thanks goes out to my Tita Fe, Tito Ram, Mom and Dad for funding this. Its been 2-weeks and already the experience has taught me so much more than simulating it on my local network.</p>

<p>As usual, I&#39;ve been busy.. powering through the new year&#39;s weeks learning about stuff and trying it out. This week I gave my desktop a facelift: desktop&#39;s color scheme, revamped DWM and learned a little bit about Mercurial and Git version control systems along the way. Now my focus is on the website so expect to some changes you can see..</p>

<p>Happy New Years &#39;errbody !</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fresh & Easy's Beer Selection]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.pnd4.net/blog/2012/08/26/fresh-easys-beer-selection/"/>
    <updated>2012-08-26T16:34:08-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.pnd4.net/blog/2012/08/26/fresh-easys-beer-selection</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img class="center" src="/images/2012-08-26-fresh-easys-beer-selection/kona<em>brewing</em>company_beers-02.jpg&#8221;></p>

<p>If you ever find yourself frequenting a Fresh n&#39; Easy market like I have, hopefully you try some of the beer&#39;s they rotate into the sale&#39;s page..  I&#39;ve, more often than not, been surprised by their selection which ranges from local brews, imports, and the usual commodity of domestics. While theres nothing wrong with grabbing your favorite, a lot of us out there like to take risks and broaden our horizons. Here&#39;s a short listing of a few randoms I&#39;ve tried in the last month or two, and ratings to go with them.</p>

<p>9 / 10 - Kona Brewing Co. &#39;Longboard Island Lager&#39;</p>

<p>9 / 10 - Leffe: &#39;Leffe Blonde&#39;</p>

<p>3 / 10 - Hopper Whitman: &#39;Belgian White&#39;</p>

<p>7 / 10 - Racer5</p>

<p>Hopefully this helps someone pacing up and down the cooler isle trying to make their selection, so they can get to where they need to be and back to loving life.</p>

<p>Thanks goes out to Adriel, John, and Fresh &amp; Easy for making this post possible.. <em>hiccup</em></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defcon or Bust !!1!]]></title>
    <link href="http://www.pnd4.net/blog/2012/07/08/defcon-or-bust-1/"/>
    <updated>2012-07-08T09:19:19-04:00</updated>
    <id>http://www.pnd4.net/blog/2012/07/08/defcon-or-bust-1</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I&#39;ve decided that this summer I&#39;d like to attend Def Con 20. After watching talks from previous Def Cons and other various events over the years on-line its finally time for me to get out and physically be there. I&#39;ve been trying to head out to some &#39;talks&#39; out here in the bay area too, but since Def Con is coming right up, and I still live on the right coast, why not. Its a great opportunity to see what&#39;s new in the world of technology first hand and meet the actual people developing it all in one place.</p>

<p>If you even consider knowing me, even just a little bit, you know that I&#39;m a huge fan of this kind of stuff, and have been since primary school. I&#39;ve always tried to make myself available to help solve problems and willing to guide friends and family that have also shown interest in the area with all I can offer. Its a learning experience, every time. Like they say, &quot;Teach a man to fish and you feed him for a lifetime.&quot; Which is why I urge anyone reading this to come to with, simply because its pretty much impossible to walk out of one of these places and not be inspired.. not to mention its in Vegas :)</p>

<p>Unfortunately, at this point in my life there&#39;s a lot of free time to be spent, and life is short. Conversely, money is short-coming and school is annually getting more expensive. Education and opportunities we can all agree are valuable. Getting me to Def Con 20 isn&#39;t going to be easy, but all I have is time,`a willing mind, and a drive to be there. With a little help I&#39;m sure I&#39;ll be hacking away with the best of them out in Las Vegas at the end of the month.</p>

<p>&#8211;pnd4</p>

<p><img class="center" src="http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v159/comfreak/dc20-logo.png">  </p>

<p><a href="https://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=_donations&amp;business=7W7HS7N8WVYXJ&amp;lc=US&amp;item_name=Send%20Kevin%20to%20Defcon%2020&amp;item_number=115501337&amp;currency_code=USD&amp;bn=PP%2dDonationsBF%3adc20%2dlogo%2epng%3aNonHosted"><img class="center" src="https://www.paypalobjects.com/en<em>US/i/btn/btn</em>donateCC_LG.gif&#8221;></a></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
